Kaloyan Penev

Computer Vision Engineer



ABOUT ME

Problem-solver interested in machine learning and computer graphics. Professional experience using Unity for NCCA Bournemouth University on the VISTA AR project. Familiar with Object Oriented and Entity-Component-System programming paradigms. Adaptive and creative in team environments.

PROJECTS

HAND POSE RECOGNITION

Python / YOLOv4 / Darknet

Real-time speeds on consumer-grade GPUs using input from ordinary phone cameras. Built with the YOLOv4 FCNN.

GAME ENGINE - eudaimonia

C++17 / C / OpenGL / GLSL

Data-oriented ECS framework created in native C++17 as backbone. 3D Physically Based Renderer made with OpenGL 3.3 as graphics system.

9	+44 7500 652536
@	kdpenev@gmail.com
•	https://penev.me

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR UNITY DEVELOPER

Bournemouth University • Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

- Development and profiling of AR apps in Unity
- Performance optimization for mobile devices
- Shader programming with **HLSL** and Shader Graph

STUDENT AMBASSADOR

Bournemouth University • Sep 2018 - Present

- Active engagement in the Admissions division
- Garnered rich teamwork experience
- Improved presenting and communication skills

EDUCATION

BSc GAMES SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Bournemouth University • Sept 2018 – Jun 2021 First class Honours (Predicted)

- Graphics and Computational Programming 83.03%
- Game Engine Programming 79.00%
- Al Game Programming 75.50%

HOBBIES

Front-end web development - https://penev.me Building websites for fun. UI/UX design enthusiast.

Podcasting - https://abstractapes.com Co-host of a podcast on philosophy and science.